

Mohammad Ilyas Kohistani

Full-Stack Web Developer

- MEVLANA MAH. YILDIRIM BEYAZIT CAD. ESENYURT, 37500 Istanbul, Turkey
- 💌 alyas.kohistani@gmail.com 📞 +905526996353 🏥 Mar 20, 1998 🏲 Afghan

in linkedin.com/in/mohammad-ilyas-kohistani-81b437129 🜍 github.com/IlyasKohistani

Profile

passionate full-stack PHP web developer with over six years of experience developing web and mobile based applications. Developed a highly customizeable, risk assessment system focused on design modularity and code flexibility. Handled all steps of the development lifecycle; from requirements gathering/estimating to customer support and enhancements. Worked as part of a remote team utilizing an array of communications tools to ensure seamless results.

Professional Experience

IGW Organization, *Mobile developer* 2015 – present

IGW Organization, *Full-stack web developer* 2015 – present | Kabul, Afghanistan

AIESEC Organization, *Responsible for outgoing exchange and event manager* 2018 – 2019 | Kabul, Afghanistan

	Languages	
Persian		
English		_
Turkish		

Skills

PHP, Laravel, React, MySQL, jQuery, Ajax, Dart, Flutter, Android Studio, JavaScript, ASP.NET, SASS, CSS, HTML5, Redux, CSS Grid, CSS Flexbox, Codeigniter

Education

Kabul University,

Bachelor degree/ computer science 2016 – 2019

Ghulam Haidar Khan, *Degree of high school* 2015

Projects

Remotify, remotify.co

2020 - present

Remotify.co is a hire and find job web application developed in wojo framework.

SDROA ERP,

Mobile application for SDROA organization 2019

https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/sdroaerp/id1528045229Available on Apple Store

ROBUSTA,

Robusta coffe house management system 2019

Courses

React & Redux, *Udemy* 2020

Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations and More!, *Udemy* 2019

PHP with Laravel, *Udemy* 2016

SDROA2.ORG ☑

2019

As a UIUX designer

EventHub,

An easy event management mobile application.

Organisations

ALPHA, *Event manager* 2018 – present

AIESEC, responsible for outgoing exchanges 2017 – 2019 | Kabul, Afghanistan